mbrsolution.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy Policy - Mbrsolution

At _Mbrsolution_ , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us (See <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Privacy_policy> to learn more about Privacy Policies.). This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by _Mbrsolution_ and how it is used. **Log Files**  like many other Web sites, _Mbrsolution_ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user\'s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 ** **Cookies****

 _Mbrsolution_ uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 ** ** **Google Advertising (Adsense) Cookies******

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on _Mbrsolution_.
  * Google\'s use of cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to _Mbrsolution_ and other sites on the Internet.
  * You can learn more about how Google uses cookies in ads from the following URL - <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on _Mbrsolution_ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. _Mbrsolution_ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  

 _Mbrsolution_ \'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser\'s respective websites. 

**Contact Details**

The email addresses collected via subscriptions to the Mbrsolution Website newsletter are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties. These addresses are only used by Mbrsolution to send out information about posts updates such as, new tutorials, updated tutorials, web developing information,theme updates, IT support information and online technology. You will not receive any mailings you did not request or subscribed too. The email addresses are stored in my MailChimp account. You can read more about MailChimp GDPR Compliance from the following URL <https://blog.mailchimp.com/getting-ready-for-the-gdpr/>. 

Any data collected when a visitor checks the following Notify me of followup comments via e-mail is kept in my secured VPS server. These personal details are kept while the person is signed up. Once they unsubscribe from the post the data will be deleted. This data will never be sold, or disclosed to any third parties.Mbrsolution.com does not collect or keep any information submitted via e-mail through the contact form. This site is using WPForms Lite plugin version which does not collect any form entries. You can read more about it from the following [comment](https://wpforms.com/how-to-save-your-contact-form-data-in-wordpress-database/#comment-26824) by one of the support staff.  

 **What rights you have over your data**

If you have left comments in my blog posts, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data mbrsolution holds about you, including any data you have provided to mbrsolution. You can also request that mbrsolution erase any personal data in your subscription to comments about you. This does not include any data mbrsolution is obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

If you have questions regarding the privacy policies, or require assistance in opting out of the email lists, please contact me.
